capbeauty.com 2019-02-06

# Privacy Policy – CAP Beauty

**Effective date:** May 25, 2018

CAP Beauty ("us", "we", or "our") operates the [http://www.capbeauty.com](http://www.capbeauty.com/)  
website (the "Service").

This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use, and  
disclosure of personal data when you use our Service and the choices you have  
associated with that data.

We use your data to provide and improve the Service. By using the Service, you  
agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy.  
Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy  
Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, accessible from  

 **DEFINITIONS**

**Service**  
Service is the [http://www.capbeauty.com](http://www.capbeauty.com/) website operated by CAP Beauty

 **Personal Data**  
Personal Data means data about a living individual who can be identified  
from those data (or from those and other information either in our  
possession or likely to come into our possession).

 **Usage Data**  
Usage Data is data collected automatically either generated by the use of  
the Service or from the Service infrastructure itself (for example, the  
duration of a page visit).

 **Cookies**  
Cookies are small pieces of data stored on your device (computer or mobile  
device).

 **Data Controller**  
Data Controller means the natural or legal person who (either alone or  
jointly or in common with other persons) determines the purposes for which  
and the manner in which any personal information are, or are to be,  
processed.

For the purpose of this Privacy Policy, we are a Data Controller of your  
Personal Data.

 **Data Processors (or Service Providers)**  
Data Processor (or Service Provider) means any natural or legal person who  
processes the data on behalf of the Data Controller.

We may use the services of various Service Providers in order to process  
your data more effectively.

 **Data Subject (or User)**  
Data Subject is any living individual who is using our Service and is the  
subject of Personal Data.

 **INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE  
**  
We collect several different types of information for various purposes to  
provide and improve our Service to you.

 **Types of Data Collected**

 **Personal Data**  
While using our Service, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally  
identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you  
("Personal Data"). Personally identifiable information may include, but is not  
limited to:

* Email address  
* First name and last name  
* Phone number  
* Address, State, Province, ZIP/Postal code, City  
* Cookies and Usage Data

We may use your Personal Data to contact you with newsletters, marketing or  
promotional materials and other information that may be of interest to you.  
You may opt out of receiving any, or all, of these communications from us by  
following the unsubscribe link or instructions provided in any email we send  
or by contacting us.

 **Usage Data**  
We may also collect information how the Service is accessed and used ("Usage  
Data"). This Usage Data may include information such as your computer's  
Internet Protocol address (e.g. IP address), browser type, browser version,  
the pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the  
time spent on those pages, unique device identifiers and other diagnostic  
data.

 **Location Data**  
We may use and store information about your location if you give us permission  
to do so (“Location Data”). We use this data to provide features of our  
Service, to improve and customize our Service.

You can enable or disable location services when you use our Service at any  
time, through your device settings.

 **Tracking; Cookies Data**

We use cookies and similar tracking technologies to track the activity on our  
Service and hold certain information.

Cookies are files with small amount of data which may include an anonymous  
unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a website and stored  
on your device. Tracking technologies also used are beacons, tags, and scripts  
to collect and track information and to improve and analyze our Service.

You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a  
cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be  
able to use some portions of our Service.

 **Examples of Cookies we use:**  
Session Cookies. We use Session Cookies to operate our Service.  
Preference Cookies. We use Preference Cookies to remember your preferences  
and various settings.  
 **Security Cookies.** We use Security Cookies for security purposes.

 **Use of Data**  
CAP Beauty uses the collected data for various purposes:

* To provide and maintain our Service  
* To notify you about changes to our Service  
* To allow you to participate in interactive features of our Service when  
you choose to do so  
* To provide customer support  
* To gather analysis or valuable information so that we can improve our  
Service  
* To monitor the usage of our Service  
* To detect, prevent and address technical issues  
* To provide you with news, special offers and general information about  
other goods, services and events which we offer that are similar to those  
that you have already purchased or enquired about unless you have opted  
not to receive such information

 **Legal Basis for Processing Personal Data Under General Data Protection**  
 **Regulation (GDPR)**   
If you are from the European Economic Area (EEA), CAP Beauty legal basis for  
collecting and using the personal information described in this Privacy Policy  
depends on the Personal Data we collect and the specific context in which we  
collect it.

 _ **CAP Beauty may process your Personal Data because:**_

* We need to perform a contract with you  
* You have given us permission to do so  
* The processing is in our legitimate interests and it's not overridden by  
your rights  
* For payment processing purposes  
* To comply with the law

 **RETENTION OF DATA  
** CAP Beauty will retain your Personal Data only for as long as is necessary for  
the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy. We will retain and use your  
Personal Data to the extent necessary to comply with our legal obligations  
(for example, if we are required to retain your data to comply with applicable  
laws), resolve disputes, and enforce our legal agreements and policies.

CAP Beauty will also retain Usage Data for internal analysis purposes. Usage  
Data is generally retained for a shorter period of time, except when this data  
is used to strengthen the security or to improve the functionality of our  
Service, or we are legally obligated to retain this data for longer time  
periods.

 **TRANSFER OF DATA**  
Your information, including Personal Data, may be transferred to — and  
maintained on — computers located outside of your state, province, country or  
other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ than  
those from your jurisdiction.

If you are located outside United States and choose to provide information to  
us, please note that we transfer the data, including Personal Data, to United  
States and process it there.

Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such  
information represents your agreement to that transfer.

CAP Beauty will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data  
is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy and no transfer  
of your Personal Data will take place to an organization or a country unless  
there are adequate controls in place including the security of your data and  
other personal information.

 **DISCLOSURE OF DATA**

**Legal Requirements**  
CAP Beauty may disclose your Personal Data in the good faith belief that such  
action is necessary to:

* To comply with a legal obligation  
* To protect and defend the rights or property of CAP Beauty  
* To prevent or investigate possible wrongdoing in connection with the  
Service  
* To protect the personal safety of users of the Service or the public  
* To protect against legal liability

 **Security of Data**  
The security of your data is important to us, but remember that no method of  
transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100%  
secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your  
Personal Data, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

 **"Do Not Track" Signals**  
We do not support Do Not Track ("DNT"). Do Not Track is a preference you can  
set in your web browser to inform websites that you do not want to be tracked.

You can enable or disable Do Not Track by visiting the Preferences or Settings  
page of your web browser.

 **Your Data Protection Rights Under General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)**  
If you are a resident of the European Economic Area (EEA), you have certain  
data protection rights. CAP Beauty aims to take reasonable steps to allow you  
to correct, amend, delete, or limit the use of your Personal Data.

If you wish to be informed what Personal Data we hold about you and if you  
want it to be removed from our systems, please contact us.

 _ **In certain circumstances, you have the following data protection rights:**_

* The right to access, update or to delete the information we have on you.  
Whenever made possible, you can access, update or request deletion of your  
Personal Data directly within your account settings section. If you are  
unable to perform these actions yourself, please contact us to assist you.

* The right of rectification. You have the right to have your information  
rectified if that information is inaccurate or incomplete.

* The right to object. You have the right to object to our processing of  
your Personal Data.

* The right of restriction. You have the right to request that we restrict  
the processing of your personal information.

* The right to data portability. You have the right to be provided with a  
copy of the information we have on you in a structured, machine-readable  
and commonly used format.

* The right to withdraw consent. You also have the right to withdraw your  
consent at any time where CAP Beauty relied on your consent to process  
your personal information.

Please note that we may ask you to verify your identity before responding to  
such requests.

You have the right to complain to a Data Protection Authority about our  
collection and use of your Personal Data. For more information, please contact  
your local data protection authority in the European Economic Area (EEA).

 **SERVICE PROVIDERS**  
We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service  
("Service Providers"), to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform  
Service-related services or to assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.

These third parties have access to your Personal Data only to perform these  
tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other  
purpose.

 **ANALYTICS**    
We may use third-party Service Providers to monitor and analyze the use of our  
Service.

 **Google Analytics**  
Google Analytics is a web analytics service offered by Google that tracks  
and reports website traffic. Google uses the data collected to track and  
monitor the use of our Service. This data is shared with other Google  
services. Google may use the collected data to contextualize and  
personalize the ads of its own advertising network.

You can opt-out of having made your activity on the Service available to  
Google Analytics by installing the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-  
on. The add-on prevents the Google Analytics JavaScript (ga.js,  
analytics.js, and dc.js) from sharing information with Google Analytics  
about visits activity.

For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the  
Google Privacy & Terms web page: [https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en](https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en)

 **BEHAVIORAL REMARKETING  
** CAP Beauty uses remarketing services to advertise on third party websites to  
you after you visited our Service. We and our third-party vendors use cookies  
to inform, optimize and serve ads based on your past visits to our Service.

 **Google AdWords**  
Google AdWords remarketing service is provided by Google Inc.

You can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize  
the Google Display Network ads by visiting the Google Ads Settings page:  
<http://www.google.com/settings/ads>

Google also recommends installing the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser  
Add-on (<https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>) for your web  
browser. Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on provides visitors with  
the ability to prevent their data from being collected and used by Google  
Analytics.

For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the  
Google Privacy & Terms web page: <https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en>

 **FACEBOOK**  
Facebook remarketing service is provided by Facebook Inc.

You can learn more about interest-based advertising from Facebook by  
visiting this page: <https://www.facebook.com/help/164968693837950>

To opt-out from Facebook's interest-based ads follow these instructions  
from Facebook: <https://www.facebook.com/help/56813749330221>7

Facebook adheres to the Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral  
Advertising established by the Digital Advertising Alliance. You can also  
opt-out from Facebook and other participating companies through the  
[Digital Advertising Alliance in the USA](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/), t[he Digital Advertising Alliance of](http://youradchoices.ca/)  
[ Canada in Canada](http://youradchoices.ca/)  or the [European Interactive Digital Advertising Alliance in Europe](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/), or opt-out using your mobile device settings.

For more information on the privacy practices of Facebook, please visit  
Facebook's Data Policy: [https://www.facebook.com/privacy/explanation](https://www.facebook.com/privacy/explanation)

 **PAYMENTS**  
We may provide paid products and/or services within the Service. In that case,  
we use third-party services for payment processing (e.g. payment processors).

We will not store or collect your payment card details. That information is  
provided directly to our third-party payment processors whose use of your  
personal information is governed by their Privacy Policy. These payment  
processors adhere to the standards set by PCI-DSS as managed by the PCI  
Security Standards Council, which is a joint effort of brands like Visa,  
Mastercard, American Express and Discover. PCI-DSS requirements help ensure  
the secure handling of payment information.

The payment processors we work with are:

 **Apple Store In-App Payments**  
Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at https://www.apple.com/legal/privacy  
/en-ww/

 **Stripe**  
Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at <https://stripe.com/us/privacy>

 **LINKS TO OTHER SITES**  
Our Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If  
you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party's  
site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you  
visit.

We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy  
policies or practices of any third party sites or services.

 **CHILDREN'S PRIVACY**  
Our Service does not address anyone under the age of 18 ("Children").

We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone  
under the age of 18. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that  
your child has provided us with Personal Data, please contact us. If we become  
aware that we have collected Personal Data from children without verification  
of parental consent, we take steps to remove that information from our  
servers.

 **CHANGES TO THIS POLICY**  
We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any  
changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.

We will let you know via email and/or a prominent notice on our Service, prior  
to the change becoming effective and update the "effective date" at the top of  
this Privacy Policy.

You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes.  
Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this  
page.

 **CONTACT US**  
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us:

 **By email:[heybeautiful@capbeauty.com](mailto:heybeautiful@capbeauty.com)**
